Right now — somewhere in India —
an old man is being told he is under arrest.
A voice says his name is in a money-laundering case.
"Stay on the line. Don't tell your family.
Transfer the money to clear your name."
By the time anyone notices…
his life's savings are gone.
This is the digital-arrest scam.
Last year it stole Rs 19,000 crore —
one phone call at a time.
Every tool built to stop it protects the bank —
not the frightened person on the call.
It warns them on a screen…
but the people losing everything often can't read it.
So we built Kavach.
A shield on the phone he already owns.
No internet. No cloud. Nothing leaves the device —
airplane mode, the entire time.
Kavach never asks "is the voice fake."
It listens for the script every scammer uses —
urgency, secrecy, "send money to a safe account," fake police.
Watch it follow the call. Safe…
then careful, as the pressure builds…
and the moment it is certain—
[  Kavach speaks the warning aloud — in Hindi  ]
"Stop. This may be a scam — don't send money
or share any code. Hang up and call family."
It doesn't just flash a red screen.
It speaks. Out loud. In his own language.
For a man who cannot read that warning,
this voice is the hand that says: stop.
And it's real — not a trick.
Tap it, and Kavach shows the exact words
that gave the scam away —
its reasoning, running entirely on the phone.
No servers. No subscription.
Twelve languages, on a Rs 6,000 phone —
for the people who need it most.
Our parents. Our grandparents.
Kavach. It catches the script… not the voice.
And it speaks up — before the money is gone.